{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Wàipó" ,
      "answer": "外婆"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nín",
      "answer": "您"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhè" ,
      "answer": "这"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tā",
      "answer": "他"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wàiyǔ",
      "answer": "外语"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīshēng",
      "answer": "医生"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nǎinai",
      "answer": "奶奶"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shì",
      "answer": "是"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nà",
      "answer": "那"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nǎ",
      "answer": "哪"
    },
    {
      "question": "Guó",
      "answer": "国"
    },
    {
      "question": "Rén",
      "answer": "人"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shéi",
      "answer": "谁"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lǎoshī",
      "answer": "老师"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dōu",
      "answer": "都"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhōngguó",
      "answer": "中国"
    }
  ]
}
